{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is correct about TypeScript?",
      "options": [
        "Angular is based on TypeScript.",
        "This is a superset of JavaScript.",
        "TypeScript is maintained by Microsoft.",
        "All of the above."
      ],
      "answer": "All of the above."
    },
    {
      "question": "What does AOT stand for?",
      "options": [
        "Ahead-Of-Time Compilation",
        "Angular Object Templates",
        "Both",
        "None of the above "
      ],
      "answer": "Ahead-Of-Time Compilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which file is responsible for startup of angular project ?",
      "options": [
        "main.ts",
        "index.ts",
        "app.js",
        "angular.json"
      ],
      "answer": "main.ts"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which character is used for chaining multiple pipes in Angular ?",
      "options": [
        ":",
        "-",
        "/",
        "|"
      ],
      "answer": "|"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following filter is used to convert input to all uppercase ?",
      "options": [
        "upper",
        "toUpper",
        "uppercase",
        "toUpperCase"
      ],
      "answer": "uppercase"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a hook in Angular application life cycle ?",
      "options": [
        "ngOnChanges",
        "ngOnInit",
        "ngAfterViewInit",
        "ngViewStart"
      ],
      "answer": "ngViewStart"
    },
    {
      "question": "Angular does not provide nested components.",
      "options": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "RxJS can be used for ?",
      "options": [
        "Client Side",
        "Server Side",
        "Both ",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Both "
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following service has Angular 2, that allows us to dynamically load a component in a certain position on the page ?",
      "options": [
        "DynamicComponentLoader",
        "DynamicControlLoader",
        "DynamicControllerLoader",
        "DynamicControllerLoad"
      ],
      "answer": "DynamicComponentLoader"
    },
    {
      "question": "Observables help you manage ___________ data ",
      "options": [
        "Synchronous",
        "Asynchronous",
        "Both  ",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "answer": "Asynchronous"
    }
  ]
}
